Enjoy the Resort to the Fullest
A resort!
Hup!
And a super landing.
Stop jumping. You'll trip and fall.
I'm glad all these State Security Service
officers are keeping an eye out for the bomber.
But I keep feeling like I'm being
stared at, and it's insanely distracting.
Papa.
I've heard that at times like this,
normal papas would also jump and play
and have fun with their daughters.
Let's go enjoy this resort to the fullest!
Papa's such a pushover.
Mama!
Yor...
You got our message?
Yes.
I was given the day off today.
Your face seems a little swollen.
Huh?
He figured it out.
Are you all right?
Oh, um...
The couple we were entertaining
got into an argument...
and when I got between them to stop them, uh...
I see...
So then the deal...
Yes, it fell through.
But we did everything we could.
And in the end, the couple was smiling.
So I'm happy with the results!
I see.
Can Mama play today?
Yes! Let's make sure to play lots!
Let's enjoy!
Enjoy we shall!
They look like Bond!
Everything's so peaceful here. It's nice.
Indeed.
Though being on that ship
was rather ominous.
I hope peaceful days like
this will continue forever.
And to make that happen, I'll...
Papa! Mama!
I wanna do the thing where you go into
the ocean and look at fishies next!
Huh?! You have to wear a
swimsuit for this, don't you?
Oh, no... If they see the wound on my chest,
I won't be able to talk myself out of it.
Actually, we might get eaten
by sharks, so never mind.
Huh?! But...
Oh, I might be able to cover
it with this swimsuit.
Let's give it a try, Miss Anya!
Don't worry. There are no sharks.
Even if there are,
I'll secretly beat them up.
Ba bwishies bar bo bretty!
The fishies are so pretty!
Bes. Bey book bo beliblous!
Yes. They look so delicious!
Anya wants to go surfing next!
Let's do it!
Here comes a great wave, Miss Anya!
Okee!
I'll give you a little push.
There!
Oh, no! I just finished a job,
so my sense of strength is still off!
Ooh!
Are you all right, Miss Anya?!
I wanna do that again!
So thrilling!
Don't.
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
We played lots!
We sure did!
It's just about time. We should
head back to the ship.
You're right.
Oh...
I've been fighting without sleep or rest,
so I'm suddenly very sleepy.
Um... Yor?
Papa... Anya's sleepy, too.
Tired now.
Huh?!
Anya's one thing, but Yor, too?
I'm guessing this job was
pretty rough on her.
And yet, she did her best to go
along with Anya's requests...
You did a great job.
Souvenirs
This incident on the Lorelei...
Though it hasn't been announced publicly,
apparently, a lot of
passengers went missing.
All of them had forged IDs.
I did indeed see a number of
suspicious-looking characters.
If any are involved in instigating
conflict between the East and West,
we should look into them.
Apparently the State Security Service thinks
there's another country involved in this.
I'm sure they're going to erase any trace
of this incident happening, though.
We'll just keep our eye out for any
extremists in Ostania on our end.
This would involve Strix, as well.
I'm counting on you.
Understood.
So...
Putting aside the bombing incident,
how was your vacation?
Was little Anya happy?
I've had enough vacations. They're far
more backbreaking than my usual missions.
I can never tell if he's
actually clever or clumsy.
Bragging About Vacation
Good morning.
Oh, Yor. You're back already?
Jeez, Yor. No fair that only you got to go!
Where's my souvenir from the cruise?
Again, she was entertaining guests.
Yes. I found a very lovely
souvenir on the cruise!
Here it is!
What... is this thing?
It's a skeleton keychain.
Oof, this is the worst.
I definitely don't want this.
What is wrong with your taste?
Usually, people would get
their coworkers wine,
snacks, or other consumables
for souvenirs, wouldn't they?
O-Oh, I see!
Papa wouldn't buy me this.
Mama, buy this for me.
I clearly said I'd buy that for her, didn't I?
This is very cool, Miss Anya.
I'll get these as souvenirs
for Camilla and the others.
What should I do?
Loid picked out some snacks for Yuri's gift.
Should I just give them those?
There won't be enough for everyone, though.
Well... I can't say I didn't expect this from you.
What? Wine totally would've been better.
I guess I'll give it to my kid.
Skip, skip, la, la, la!
La, la, la! La, la, la! La, la, la...
You seem to be a good mood, Yuri.
Did something happen with your sister?
I'm surprised you knew
this was about my sister!
Are you some kind of psychic?
Maybe.
My sister's back from her business trip!
I'm going to stop by my
sister's place after work!
It's been so long since
I've seen Sis! Sis! Sis!
But if she's back, that also means...
He's back.
That should do it.
It's quite a pain to prepare all this
every time her brother comes over.
But despite him being a relative,
he's an officer of the State Security Service,
the arch-nemesis of WISE.
Letting my guard down even
a little may cost me dearly.
It'll probably look more convincing if
I move the pillows closer together.
I should also add more recent family photos.
Maybe I should prepare matching
pajamas, too, just in case.
Hey, did you go anywhere during the break?
I went to see Pecasso's works
at the art museum.
I went to the National Opera
House and saw an orchestra.
How cool.
Good day, Anya!
Heh. Morning, please.
Oh? You look a little tanned.
Did you go somewhere?
Heh. Are you sure you want
to ask me that, little lady?
It's a long story, but yes, that day,
Anya was on the ocean.
It was the start of an epic adventure.
Who is she trying to be here?
Anya has now been aboard...
a luxury cruise ship!
Wait, what did you say?!
What?!
Anya, you're such a celebrity!
Wait, are you serious?! You really
got to ride that legendary ship?!
Hey, you. You need to think better of Anya.
I was wrong, Miss Anya!
The Holgers definitely deserve
to come over to my place!
Come over!
Anya is a skilled agent who
doesn't forget the mission.
Aw, that's pretty normal.
Shock!
It's not normal at all! It was super huge!
It was called Prindess Lalalai, or something!
You mean the Princess Lorelei? I rode
on it there before I enrolled here.
It was okay, I guess.
Shock!
We stayed in the imperial suite, but the
furnishings didn't quite do it for me.
Shock!
Anya stayed in a jail cell in third class...
Pfft!
If I stayed in third class, I'd be
too embarrassed to talk about it.
Hey, quit it. I feel bad for the commoners.
Just the other day, I got to
fly over Münk in a helicopter.
It was so much fun!
We stayed at a luxury hotel in Bayan,
and I ate tons of yummy things!
Hmph. So what?
I got my papa to let me have a party with
the actress from Berlint in Love, Rachel.
There were about a hundred people there,
and I got to hear behind-the-scenes stories
and received presents.
It was just so much fun!
That's amazing, Becky!
The Blackbells sure are amazing!
You're on another level!
Hey, tell us more about Rachel!
Was she pretty in person?
Introduce me to her!
Yeah, well, on Anya's ship...
There were, like, a hundred
really insane people!
What do you mean by that?
Were there, like, celebrities onboard?
Ooh. Like who?
Apparently, some came from
another country, too!
Huh...
Wait, so foreign celebrities?
Wow!
Well, don't keep us waiting! Tell us who!
You know...
Like Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby.
Who?!
Who the heck's that? Never heard of them.
A street performer?
Well, who else was there?
Huh?
Um...
There was Thwomp-man,
who commanded elephants...
Lies
And Shwoop-man, who could teleport.
Who even are these people? A circus?
Um... Bad guys.
Bad guys? Really?
What? Did you run into some pirates?
That must've sucked!
I didn't hear anything like that on the news.
Don't take her seriously.
That's right!
The incident with the bad guys
will never see the light of day!
I can't believe I got my hopes up.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
They weren't on the news.
That's because they're a
bunch of secret bad guys that
even the government doesn't know about!
The truth is they came from the
bottom of the ocean... They were...
The octopeople!
The great hero Anya secretly defeated
them one by one with the stabby thing!
Actually, Mama did.
So, what did you and Rachel talk about?
Introduce me to her!
Shock!
And so... the peace of the
world... was protec...
No way! Samantha was there, too?!
No fair! I want to meet them, too!
Wow, she sure is something.
She's such a grandiose liar.
I guess in one way, she's a hero.
At least you never get bored watching her.
What the heck is an octoperson
who commands elephants?
Right?
All right, everyone. Get to your seats.
Did you all enjoy your break?
Sir, apparently Forger
defeated some octopeople.
Wow, that's amazing.
I totally understand.
We humans are creatures that
try to embellish things
at times so we look even better.
But if you just work hard to
get closer to your ideal self,
you'll become a lovely lady.
That's what my mama told me.
Becky!
But you should be careful about lying
or you'll end up a loner like me.
Ah! It's been so long, Sis!
It's been too long!
Souvenirs
Here you go. I bought you some snacks.
Wow! I'll treasure them forever!
Make sure you eat them
before they expire, though.
Then I'll take a picture of them
and admire it every single day!
He's so loud.
Borf!
Anya has returned.
Welcome home!
Oh? What's the matter, Miss Anya?
Borboborf?
You tried to act like a celebrity
and got made fun of?
They called me a liar.
Anya cried a little.
Why would you lie like that?
For Plan B!
How do you know about that?!
Because I wanted to stand out.
If you let your emotions take
over and tell careless lies,
you'll get burned.
If you're going to create
a persona for yourself,
you need to be strategic and commit.
Stake your life on it!
First, you need to gather enough
details to make your lie convincing,
and work in some truth here and there.
But be extravagantly...
I see. Right... I see.
But lying isn't good.
I've seen so many of them
throughout my life.
Those who lie are nothing but trash.
They're all just filth, nothing more
than vermin infesting our country!
Me? The only reason I'm lying
about who I am is for my sister!
Everything I do for my sister is righteous!
Only trash tells lies.
R-Right...
Of course, you want to be true
to yourself whenever you can.
I'm sure you'll be able to get
along with everyone! Yes!
Lying is too much work,
so I'll try not to do it anymore.
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
Berlint in Love
Nightfall's Daily Life